You're awake.
I made you breakfast.
Are you crazy?
What do you want?
I'm protecting you.
Protecting me?
You knocked me out
and brought me to your house.
This used to be your home too.
Pei Song.
We are already divorced.
Today is the day I marry Pei Ning.
I've told you many times.
I don't know how to explain it.
Someone wants to...
This is kidnapping.
I can call the police.
It's useless to trap me here.
The person I love is Pei Ning.
I am going to marry him.
You just can't compare to him.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Did you just say
I can't compare to Pei Ning?
I can't compare to Pei Ning, right?
Don't touch me.
Just stay here and behave.
I'll let you go after today.
Make do with this.
I'm not good at cooking.
I only have instant noodles at home.
Pei Song, stop messing around.
Are we playing house or something?
Do you want it spicy?
How much should I add?
Is this enough?
Give me back my phone.
I promise you.
I won't go to the wedding.
But I have to call Pei Ning to let him know.
I will tell him for you.
Green onions, cilantro.
I remember you don't eat green onions.
Give me back my phone.
Give me my phone, car keys,
and wallet.
Stab me.
Let me go.
Put me down.
Pei Song.
Let me go.
Stay here and behave.
I'll let you go after today.
Brother.
Growing up,
why is everything I own
You want to take everything away.
Shiya,
get up and eat something.
Shiya.
Shiya,
are you asleep?
Get up and eat something.
Shiya.
Didn't expect this, did you?
Fang Jingyan.
Why are you here?
Where is Song Shiya?
I let Shiya go.
Let her go? Are you crazy?
Do you know what you're doing?
I'm helping my bestie
escape the control of her psychotic ex-husband.
I was protecting her.
Someone is trying to kill her at the wedding.
I'm so scared.
Fang Jingyan!
Dude, you've watched too many dramas,
or do you think I'm a three-year-old?
At least make up a believable excuse.
Even though I don't want her to marry Pei Ning,
a girl like Shiya is better off single.
But you still can't interfere with her
Are you done?
freedom of choice. What's wrong with you?
Fang Jingyan!
I don't have time to mess around with you.
Tell me where Shiya is.
You hid her in the closet, didn't you?
You and Shiya are already divorced.
Stop bothering her.
Get out of the way.
You'll only make Shiya hate you more by doing this.
I'll tell you one last time.
I am protecting her.
Shiya, run!
Pei Song is here!
Shiya.